A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
A massacre.
（佐藤(さとう)）
大量虐殺だよ
（中野攻(なかのこう)）
あっ！
（消防士）
逃げろ！
Run!
（消防士）
お前しか佐藤を止められない！
You're the only one who can stop Sato now!
（攻）
マジかよっ！
You gotta be kidding!
No, that one back there.
He can see the IBM walk by.
（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
この奥の男だ
横切るＩＢＭが見えてる
（男性）
中野攻君だね？
-You're Ko Nakano, right?
-Don't let him get away!
（平沢(ひらさわ)）
逃がすな！
（攻）
やばい やばい やばい！
Damn, damn, damn!
Run him over.
（戸崎）はねろ
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）え？
（戸崎）
嫌なら代われ
I'll do it if you won't.
That's not the direction Sato was...
（攻）
佐藤がいた方向じゃない
Then, who is it?
じゃ 誰なんだ？
And to the humans who think
this doesn't involve you...
（テレビ音声:佐藤）
無関係だと思っている人間たち
it's just about to begin...
いよいよ始まるぞ
so, brace yourselves.
衝戟(しょうげき)に備えろ
That was a video threat uploaded
by the man who calls himself Sato.
（アナウンサー）
以上が 佐藤と名乗る男が―
インターネット上に
アップロードした犯行予告です
He announced that he will attack
Grant Pharmaceuticals
佐藤は
10日後の水曜午後３時に―
on Wednesday, ten days from now,
at 3:00 p.m.
グラント製薬の本社ビルを
襲撃するとの予告を出しており
警察及び各関係機関は―
Police and associated agencies
are joining forces to increase security.
総力を挙げて
警備強化に努めるとしています
また
警視庁の発表によりますと―
According to police,
the video upload was passed through
servers in Russia and China
アップロードされた動画はロシアや
中国のサーバーを経由しており
making it extremely difficult
to pinpoint the source.
発信元を特定するのは 極めて
困難な状況にあるとのことです
In addition, the police are investigating
the case of Kei Nagai,
さらに 警視庁では
先日 研究所から逃走し―
who escaped the laboratory just days ago
and may have left the country.
国外へ出たともいわれる永井圭(ながいけい)と
佐藤との関連も視野に入れて―
捜査を進めるということです
They hope to discover
his connection to Sato.
This has been the afternoon news.
以上 お昼のニュースでした
AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Do you sleep well?
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
They say I tried to die without knowing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分を変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
They are just wandering through life
回り道して生きているって
目立たないように
So I don't stand out
堪えられるように
So I can put up with it
So my train of thought won't stop yet
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
Tonight run away, run a way
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY  RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
Someone take my hand
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
見えない明日は来なくていい
今はただ 眠りたい
Now I just want to sleep
WAIT, LET'S TALK IT OVER
（攻）
はぁ… はぁ… はぁ…
はぁっ… はぁっ… はぁっ…
はっ！
あぁ…
I'm sorry to have caused you
so much trouble.
（圭ＩＢＭ）
お手数おかけして すみません
Be quiet.
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
黙ってろ
I've gotta pee.
（圭ＩＢＭ）
おしっこしたい…
（圭）
もう… うるさいなぁ
Just shut up!
あっ…
That's Kei Nagai!
永井… 圭
えっ？
（圭）
あっ 待て！　やめろ！
Wait! Stop!
ああっ うわっ！
（攻）
ぐわぁっ…
（圭）
あ…
（圭ＩＢＭ）
ざまあみろ
Serves you right.
ああ…　なんてことすんだ
Why did you do that?
もう…　命令は無視するし
うるさいし 血の気も多いし…
Damn it! You ignore my orders,
you won't shut up, you're bloodthirsty.
Be quiet.
（圭ＩＢＭ）
黙ってろ…
（圭）
お前が黙れ
You be quiet!
Damn. It would be so useful
if I could control him like Mr. Sato does.
ったく 佐藤さんみたく
動かせたら便利なのに
う… ていうか まずいぞ
この人 誰だ？
Now, this is a real problem.
Who is this guy?
う… こいつ
He's...
おおっ… あっ… ああっ…
うう…
My name's... Nakano.
俺は… 中野…
Ko Nakano.
中野攻だ
You're...
お前 永井圭だよな？
Kei Nagai, right?
ニュースじゃ研究員を突き落とした
みたいな言い方してたけど
The news made it sound like
you pushed the researcher off the roof,
but you were saving him.
あれは助けてた
You stood up to Sato, right?
佐藤と対立したんだろ？
So, you've seen
what Mr. Sato's really like?
佐藤さんの本性を見たのか？
Yeah.
ああ 佐藤や
政府のやつらから逃げてきた
I escaped from Sato
and those government guys.
他に当てはない
手伝ってくれ　やつを止める
I need your help. You have to.
I'm gonna stop him.
（圭）
うーん…
Come on! We can't let him do this!
あいつは野放しにしちゃいけない
Okay.
分かった
This isn't a good place.
Let's go farther in.
ここじゃ なんだし
もうちょっと奥へ行こう
I'll show you.
案内するよ
ああ！　はぁっ…
腹 減ったなぁ
I'm starving.
Hey, you got anything to eat?
なあ 何か食う物ない？
I'll bring you something later.
後で持ってきてやるよ
Here's what you asked for.
（猫沢(ねこざわ)）
頼まれていた物です
EXPLOSIVES
（佐藤）
いつも悪いね 無理言っちゃって
Sorry for always making
such difficult requests.
No, this one wasn't that difficult at all.
（猫沢）
なに こんな物
無理のうちに入りませんよ
-How's this?
-It's good.
どうかな？
（奥山(おくやま)）
いいね　これだけあれば十分だ
This is all that we'll need.
Are you sure we can keep the car, too?
（佐藤）
ホントに車まで
もらっちゃって いいの？
（猫沢）
ええ 名義はダミー会社のものに
しといたんで 足はつきません
Yeah. I've put it under the name
of a dummy company,
so, it can't be traced.
I also went ahead
and prepared the building.
あとは 例の物件も手配済みです
今日にも入れますよ
You can go today, if you like.
Excellent, that's quite a big help.
I appreciate it.
いやぁ 助かるよ　何から何まで
I've got something a little extra
for you, too.
こっちも
ちょっとサービスしといたから
Are you sure? That's quite a lot.
（猫沢）
いいんですか？　こんなに…
（佐藤）
ハハッ… 仲間が増えたからね
I've got more guys with me now.
フッ あたしらでも
お上(かみ)とだけはケンカしませんぜ
Of course, you know that even we
can't fight with the government.
Mr. Nekozawa, this isn't a fight.
猫沢さん これはケンカじゃない
This is a war.
戦争だよ
（圭）
ああ もう… 結構 難しいんだな
This is actually pretty hard.
（舌打ち）
Oh, Kei, are you going out again?
（山中(やまなか)）
あら 圭君　また お出かけ？
あ うん　ちょっと散歩
Yeah, just for a walk.
（攻）
あぁ…
（ため息）
（腹の鳴る音）
あぁ… おっせえなあ
He's late.
Sorry about that.
（圭）
悪かったね
（攻）
あ？
It took longer than I thought.
いろいろ 手間取っちゃってね
静かで いい場所でしょ？
It's nice and quiet here, isn't it?
So, you didn't get swept out after all.
案外 流されてなかったんだな
On TV, they've been saying
you may have left the country.
テレビじゃ“国外に行って
しまったんじゃ”とか言ってたのに
うん 東京湾からすら出なかった
Yeah, I didn't even leave Tokyo Bay.
（攻）
どうやって生活してるんだ？
Where are you living out here?
A woman named Mrs. Yamanaka's
letting me stay with her.
今は 山中さんって人の家に
住まわせてもらってる
Finally, I found a safe zone.
ここが ようやく手に入れた
セーフゾーンだ
（富沢(とみざわ)）
ん？　誰だい？　その子
-Who's that boy?
-Damn.
（圭）
あっ やべ…
-Hello.
-He's my grandson.
どうも…
（山中）
孫だよ 孫
げ… おばあちゃん
それ うそくさい
Lady, he's never gonna buy that.
Oh, the one from Tokyo!
（富沢）ああ 東京の！
（圭）へ？
（山中）
そうなのよ
That's right.
My idiot son almost never comes to visit,
あの馬鹿息子
めったに帰ってこないのに―
but he suddenly sent the kid
all by himself.
いきなり１人で来させて
もう 大変だよ
It's such a hardship.
You say that,
そんなこと言って―
but I bet you're really happy,
Mrs. Yamanaka.
山中さんも ホントは
うれしいんじゃないのかい？
Now then, young man, don't cause
any more trouble for the police.
坊や もう警察の厄介になるなよ
Your grandmother was really worried
about you that time!
あの時 おばあちゃん
心配してたんだぞ
あ… ハハ 善処します
I'll do my best.
Just how bad of a grandson was he?
どんな孫だよ
…って件は置いとくとしても―
But I'm amazed that there isn't anyone
who knows my face out here in the country,
ちょっと田舎に来ただけで
誰も僕の顔を知らないんだ
even though it's been so widely reported.
あれだけ報道されてるのにね
You listening?
聞いてる？
うんうん 聞いてる 聞いてる
Yeah, yeah, I'm listening.
Nakano, do you really intend
to fight Mr. Sato?
中野君
本当に佐藤さんと戦うつもりなの？
Yeah.
ん？
Why?
なんで？
I know the government came for you,
君は政府に追われたからって―
but you haven't been all over the news
like I have.
僕みたく マスコミが
騒いだわけじゃないだろ
It should be a lot easier for you
to live a peaceful life.
静かに暮らしてく方法は
僕よりあると思う
You still gonna fight?
それでも やるのか？
Yes, I am. Somehow.
やるんだ　とにかく
ちっ… そう
I see.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
僕には理解出来ないね
え？
うっ… うう… うっ ああっ…
They're ibotengu mushrooms.
They grow all over the place here.
（圭）
イボテングタケだよ
この辺りで よく採れるんだ
毒キノコだけど食うとうまい
They're poisonous, but they taste good.
The poison starts to take effect
after about 20 minutes.
大体 20分程度で中毒症状が出る
It causes stomachache, vomiting,
hallucinations,
腹痛･おう吐
幻覚･けいれん･精神錯乱
convulsions, and confusion.
最後は意識不明
Then, finally, unconsciousness.
Even if you can't die,
there are ways of disabling you.
不死身でも
無力化する方法はあるんだよ
ここは ようやく手に入れた
セーフゾーンだ
Finally, I found a safe zone of my own.
Now that you've learned where I am,
Nakano,
野放しにしちゃいけないのは
僕の居場所を知ったお前の方だよ
you're the one I can't leave unchecked.
中野
うおっ…
（うめき声）
むちゃなやつ
Why would he do that?
はっ！　あっちは…
Of course. I get it.
He's gonna try to reset!
あいつ…　リセットする気だ！
はぁっ… はぁっ… はぁっ…
おおっ…
あっ… がぁっ…
だぁっ… うわー！
ううっ…
はっ！
Nagai, wait!
Let's talk it over one more time!
永井 待て！
もう一度 話し合おう
Plan B, concussion.
（圭）
第２案 脳振盪(のうしんとう)
軽度なら数秒 重度なら数時間
意識喪失させられる
A light one may knock him out
for just seconds,
while a serious one could be hours.
（攻）
うわっ ぐっ…
待てって！
-I said, wait!
-I'll aim for the chin.
（圭）
今度は あご
Damn it. I'm warning you!
くそ！ 無力化 無力化って…
How do you do that thing again?!
どうやるんだっけな あれ！
It was popular back in junior high.
中学ん時 はやった… くっ…
ぐっ…
（圭）
失神ゲームか
Oh, the fainting game.
（攻）
うわっ がっ…
あーっ！
うっ…
はっ！
You just...
こいつ…
はっ…
いってぇ がっ…
（圭）
第３案
Plan C...
ああっ…
窒息
suffocation.
１ ２ ３…
One, two, three...
窒息死には段階がある
Suffocation works in stages.
A few seconds mostly has no effect.
数十秒なら ほぼ無症状
30秒から１分で急性呼吸困難
At 30 to 60 seconds
there's acute respiratory distress.
（うめき声）
ううっ…
At one to three minutes,
convulsions, unconsciousness, and coma.
１分から３分で
けいれん･意識消失･昏睡(こんすい)
...155, 156...
155 156…
Yeah, the point is that it takes time
before it actually kills you.
そう ポイントは 死ぬまでに
時間がかかるというところだ
（圭）
う… ああ…
ふぅ…
So, from today on, this is our new home.
（佐藤）
さあ
今日から ここが新しいホームだ
がぁっ… はっ…
（ぶつかる音）
（攻）がっ…
うっ… いってぇ…
がぁっ！　はぁ… はぁ…
ええ？
は？
Have you revived?
復活したか？
ここは？
What is this?
This is an abandoned truck.
これは不法投棄されたトラックだ
You jerk! Let me out!
馬鹿！　出せ！
I've already done you a favor.
（圭）
これでもサービスしてる方だ
I could have left you disabled
for a lifetime.
お前を生涯無力化する方法も
あったんだぞ
If you don't want to be reported,
then let me out!
（攻）
通報されたくなきゃ
ここから出せ…　えっ？
あ あれ？
Looking for your cell phone?
（圭）
携帯なら もらったよ
あっ！？
くっ…
Nagai, are you really not going
to do anything?
永井 お前
本当に何もしないのか？
Sato's going to kill people.
佐藤は 大勢 殺すぞ
So, why are you in Japan?
じゃあ なんで日本なんかにいる？
は？
Somewhere in the world,
（圭）
いつだって世界のどこかで―
there are always people dying from war
or poverty or other absurd reasons.
戦争や貧困で理不尽に人は死んでる
Why aren't you trying to save them?
なんで 彼らを助けようとしない？
う…
Right. So, whatever happens
to some strangers here,
そう　日本のどこかで
他人がどうなろうと―
it doesn't matter to me.
僕も知ったこっちゃない
Then, why did you rescue that researcher?
じゃあ
なんで あの研究員を助けた？
あ…
I thought about that
for a long time myself.
それについては
僕も ずっと考えてた
And I was left with one question.
かつ １つの答えに帰結した
Is someone useful?
He was sympathetic to Ajins.
利用価値の有無だ
彼は亜人の理解者だった
それでいて 政府側に
属しているというのは―
And it's also important
that he's part of the government.
ポイントが高い
１～２回死んで 助ける価値はある
So, it was worth dying to save him.
Any more questions?
他に質問は？
You jerk. Let me out!
馬鹿　出せ！
ちっ…
See you. There's no point in struggling.
じゃあね　暴れても無駄だぞ
Even a black ghost couldn't
break these walls too easily.
黒い幽霊でも
この壁は簡単には破壊出来ない
You can do your business
through the little hole there.
隅に小さな穴があるから
そこで用を足せ
（攻）
ああ？　あ…
Oh, right.
（圭）あ そうだ
（攻）あ？
I'll bring you a magazine or two.
雑誌か何かを持ってきてやるよ
Humans can lose their minds
after about 72 hours with nothing to do.
何もない空間じゃ 人間の精神は
72時間しかもたないからな
（攻）
なっ！　あっ… んん…
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
くそっ！
くそっ！　くそっ！　くそっ！
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
What is wrong with him?
何なんだ あいつ…
What is wrong with him?!
何なんだ あいつ！
Now then, as I've said many times already,
（役員）
ですから 何度も
申し上げているとおり―
there's absolutely no truth to the rumor
that we've conducted experiments on Ajins.
亜人に対して―
人体実験が行われたなどという
事実はございません
Hold on. You have seen the website,
haven't you?!
（記者）
例のサイトは
ご覧になってますよね？
The threat from the self-proclaimed Ajin,
Sato.
自称 亜人の男
佐藤の犯行予告です
その中で
“グラント製薬は―”
He specifically said
that Grant Pharmaceuticals
“亜人の人体実験に関与している”
と言ってるんですよ！
conducts experiments on Ajins there!
That's...
an entirely groundless accusation.
それは…
事実無根のでたらめです
What about the incident
where Kei Nagai pushed a researcher,
（記者）
永井圭が研究員を突き落とし
重症を負わせた件はどうなんですか
seriously injuring him?!
That's right! It must be because
something awful was done to him!
（記者）
そうだ！
余程のことがあったからだろ！
（記者）
あらゆる事象が人体実験を
肯定してるじゃないですか！
Aren't there multiple sources
that point to Ajin experimentation?!
By the time
Kei Nagai was brought to the lab,
永井圭は研究所に運ばれた時
既に情緒不安定でした
he was already emotionally unstable,
the result of the media,
and their relentless...
それは メディアや
それに触発された心ない人たちに…
Damn it. The media's making a fuss.
What are you going to do, Tosaki?!
（若井(わかい)）
くそ マスコミが騒いでる
どうするんだ？　戸崎！
I agree that they are a nuisance.
Value in Japanese journalism is long dead.
確かに マスコミは厄介ですが
日本の報道の価値は既に死んでます
All but a small fraction of the public
are well aware of this.
一般人も 一部を除いて
大半が それに気づいてますよ
その一部が うるさいんだよ
But that fraction is persistent.
These idiots believe
any nonsense they're told!
くだらない情報を
真に受ける馬鹿どもがな
That may be true, but that's not what
we should be discussing right now.
だとしても それは
今 議論すべきことではありません
Then what should we be discussing?
（コウマ）
じゃあ 何を議論すべきなんだ？
-Our first priority is the man in the hat.
-You're one to talk!
最優先事項は帽子への対策です
（太居(ふとい)）
何を偉そうに！
You're the one
who not only let him get in,
お前は帽子の侵入を許した上に
サンプルまで逃がしたんだぞ！
but he got away with our sample!
That's right! Do you realize
what a huge loss that was?!
そうだ！
どれほどの損失だと思ってるんだ！
I can't believe you haven't been fired!
なぜ お前がクビにならん！？
（泉）
んん…
Look at them bark.
よく吠(ほ)えるもんだ
文句ばかりで何もしない連中が…
They complain and complain,
but never actually do anything.
Excuse me. Pardon my tardiness.
（曽我部(そかべ)）
失礼します
（曽我部）
遅くなりました
人物証明に時間がかかりまして…
It took some time
to confirm my references.
あ… 曽我部
Sokabe? What are you doing here?
なぜ お前がここに？
It's difficult for me to say to someone
who's taught me so much,
お世話になった先輩には
申し上げにくいのですが―
but I was contacted by the minister.
大臣から
お声をかけていただいたんです
I may become your successor.
あなたの後任候補として
（戸崎）
なっ…
Working under you has paid off.
先輩の下についてた甲斐(かい)が
ありましたよ
（若井）
ハッ…
A natural conclusion.
（太居）
当然の結果だな
Starting today,
I'll be watching your work, sir,
今日から 先輩の仕事を監視し
逐一 報告を上げさせてもらいます
and reporting about it in detail.
仮に
問題ありと判断が下った場合…
And if it's decided
that there's a problem--
俺は お前と交代ってわけか
Then you are to take my place immediately.
No, you'll go to hell.
いえ 地獄行きでしょ
（戸崎）
んん…
Sokabe, let me give you a fair warning.
曽我部
これは お前への忠告だが―
Once you do this, you can never go back.
この一線は 後戻り出来ないぞ
Is this the time
to act so high and mighty?
先輩風 吹かせてる場合ですか？
The police will inevitably be expected
to help defend Grant Pharmaceuticals.
グラント製薬の警備は
警察が対応に当たるのが必然
As the Ajin Control Commission,
we will be involved as consultants.
我々 亜人管理委員会は―
コンサルタントとして
参加することになる
（泉）
あっ…
There's very little time left.
（曽我部）
残された時間は わずかです
Can you come up with countermeasures
for IBMs by then?
それまでにＩＢＭ対策を
ひねり出せるのですか？
くっ…
Show us that you can... Mr. Tosaki.
やってみせてくださいよ
戸崎先輩
くぅっ…
（殴る音）
How about you just tell us already?
Tell us about the IBMs.
（平沢）
いいかげん 話したらどうだ？
ＩＢＭについてだ
（オグラ･イクヤ）
はぁ… おっさん
Old man, how about you get me a cigarette?
俺は たばこが吸いたい
We've given you cigarettes.
（平沢）
たばこなら用意しただろうが
そんなもんが吸えるか
As if I could smoke that crappy brand.
（殴る音）
（オグラ）うっ…
渋って どうなる？
What's the point in holding back?
Everyone thinks you're already dead!
お前は もう
死んだことになってるんだぞ
ハハハ… 亜人ぽいな
Like an Ajin.
（殴る音）
（オグラ）がっ！
Why won't you talk?
なぜ 話さない？　研究員の前じゃ
ペラペラしゃべってたんだろ？
You wouldn't stop talking
in front of the researchers!
You still don't get it, do you?
そんなことも分からないのか？
If they're not my smokes,
they're not real cigarettes, baldy.
ＦＫ以外は
たばこじゃないんだよ ハゲ
（平沢）
うう…
（殴る音）
So, the queen has returned.
（オグラ）
女王様のご帰還か
Mr. Tosaki, maybe this guy
really doesn't know anything.
戸崎さん　こいつ 本当は
何も知らないんじゃないのか？
Even after all this, he won't talk.
これだけやって 何も話さねぇ
And anyway, we don't even know
if the information is true, right?
第一 事実かどうか
疑わしい情報なんだろ？
（殴る音）
（悲鳴）
-Show him, Shimomura.
-Right.
（戸崎）
見せてやれ 下村君
はい
（かばんを開く音）
This was on the dead bodyguard.
死んだボディーガードの私物です
He was more than just a guard.
ただの護衛ではありません
The Department of Defense.
（平沢）
“国防総省”…
Ogura wasn't accepted into their country
simply as a biophysicist.
（戸崎）
オグラ･イクヤが向こうの国で
受け入れられたのは―
生物物理学者としてではない
Whatever the basis
for this man's theories,
この男の話は
理論や根拠はともかく―
what he says is correct,
even if it is by coincidence.
言ってることは偶然にも正しい
And it was extremely helpful
in a certain field.
そして それは
ある分野で大いに役立った
That is to say, IBM countermeasures.
すなわち ＩＢＭ対策
This man's information is useful.
こいつの情報は有益だ
This is insane.
ぶっ飛んでるな
Not from a results-oriented country.
さすが 成果主義の国だよ
Shall I break another one?
もう１本 いくか？
Leave me two.
（オグラ）
２本は残しとけよ
It's a matter of life and death
for a smoker.
スモーカーには死活問題だ
-W-- Wait! I was just joking.
-So, ready to talk?
ま… 待て！　うそうそ
話す気になったか
I meant three.
Can't knock off the ash otherwise.
３本だった　灰が落とせない
（殴る音）
（悲鳴）
何なんだ お前は…
痛みに鈍いのか？
What's wrong with you?
Can't you feel pain?
Do you think you're an Ajin yourself?
亜人にでも なったつもりか？
（オグラ）
はぁ… はぁ…
フッ フハハハ…
（戸崎）
あ？
I can handle it all day.
耐えられる程度なのさ
体の痛みなんてのは
It's only physical pain.
-Mr. Tosaki, this guy won't talk.
-Why not?
戸崎さん こいつは話さないぜ
なぜ？
'Cause he's crazy.
だって イカれてる
That's right, four-eyes.
（オグラ）
そうさ メガネ
These little gestures
don't make me feel like talking at all.
こんなもんじゃあ 俺は…
話す気分にならないぜ…
There's only one thing
that can make me talk.
俺が話す条件は たった１つ
ん？
Yeah, only one.
（オグラ）
たった１つだけだ
Bring me my cigarettes.
ＦＫを持ってこい
うっ…
あ？　ＦＫ？　本気なのか？
Cigarettes?
Are you serious?
最初から言ってるだろ
I've been telling you that
since we started this dance.
They are in the car.
車にあったはずだ　持ってこい
So, go get them. Right now!
今すぐ！
あぁー
Tastes awful.
まずい
はぁ…
All right... where should we start?
さて 何から話そう
TO BE CONTINUED
If my wish would come true
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
Once again
君の心に
触れていたい
I wanna touch your heart
No matter how dark it gets
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
I'll be searching
For my one
たったひとつの
光を
And only light
As I look up to the stars
遠いけど
Even though you are far
同じ星空　見上げてる
You're looking up at the same starry sky
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
In the sky of my heart
It's about to spill over
Your smile and
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
分かってたつもりだった
What it means to love
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
本当の愛に気付いて
Realizing real love
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are
I'll tell you now